**US**

* 日本
    
* ไทย
    
* Indonesia
    
* Philippines
    
* Việt Nam
    
* Malaysia
    
* Singapore
    
* UK
    
* US

**Lemon8 Privacy Policy**
=========================

Last Updated: March 22, 2024

Welcome to Lemon8 (“Lemon8”, “we” or “us” or “our”). This Privacy Policy applies to Lemon8 services (the “Platform”), which includes the Lemon8 app and any related services accessed via any platform, website, or device that link to this Privacy Policy. This Privacy Policy explains how we collect, use, share, and otherwise process the personal information of Platform users and other individuals. The Platform is provided and controlled by Heliophilia Pte. Ltd. whose registered address is 1 Raffles Quay #26-10 Singapore 048583.

For more information about how we may collect, use, share, and otherwise process consumer health data as defined under Washington’s My Health My Data Act and other similar state laws, please refer to the [Lemon8 Consumer Health Data Privacy Policy](https://www.lemon8-app.com/legal/consumer-health-data-privacy?region=us&language=en).

If you have any questions about how we use your personal information, please contact [contact@lemon8-app.com](mailto:contact@lemon8-app.com).

**1\. What Information We Collect**
-----------------------------------

We may collect information from and about you, including information that you provide, information from other sources, and automatically collected information:

Information You Provide

When you use the Platform, you may provide some or all of the following information.

* Account and Profile Information. We may collect information that you provide when you register or set up an account on the Platform, including your username, date of birth, gender, email address and/or telephone number, and other information you add to your user profile, such as a bio or a profile photo.
* User-Generated Content. We may collect the content that you create or upload to the Platform, such as photographs, comments, and videos (“User Content”) and the associated metadata (such as when, where, and by whom the content was created). Even if you are not a user, information about you may appear in content created or published by users on the Platform. ​​We may also collect User Content through pre-loading at the time of creation, import, or upload, regardless of whether you choose to save or upload that User Content, for example, to enable you to publish images and videos faster and optimize your user experience. We also collect content (such as text, images, and video) from your device's clipboard if you choose to copy and paste content to or from the Platform or share content between it and a third party platform.
* Surveys, Research and Promotions. We may collect information that you share through surveys or your participation in challenges, research, promotions, marketing campaigns, events, or contests.
* Preferences. We may collect your settings, choices and communication preferences.
* Messages. To the extent direct messaging functionality is available in your region, we may collect messages, which include information you provide when you compose, send, or receive messages through the Platform’s messaging functionalities. That information includes the content of the message and information about the message, such as when it was sent, received, or read, and message participants. We collect this information to block spam, detect crime and to safeguard our users. Please be aware that messages you choose to send to other users of the Platform will be accessible by those users and that we are not responsible for the manner in which those users use or share the messages.
* Information When You Contact Us. When you contact us, we collect the information you send to us, including when you contact us for support.
* Verification Information. We may collect information to verify your account, such as your email address and age.

Information from Other Sources

We may receive the information described in the Privacy Policy from other sources, such as:

* Log-in, Sign-up, or Linked Services. Where available, if you choose to sign-up or log-in to the Platform using a third-party service such as Facebook, Apple, TikTok, Google, or Twitter, or link your account to a third-party service, we may collect information from the service–for example, your public profile information such as username, email, and profile picture.
* Others. We may receive information about you from others, including where you are included or mentioned in User Content, direct messages, in a complaint, appeal, request or feedback submitted to us, or if your contact information is provided to us. We may collect information about you from other publicly available sources.

Automatically Collected Information

* Usage Information. We may collect information regarding your use of the Platform, such as how you engage with the Platform and content that you view or search on the platform (e.g., your browsing history on the platform). We may also process information about your followers, the likes you receive and responses to content you upload, for the purposes of promoting your content to other users and exploring whether your profile presents further opportunities for collaboration.
* Technical Information. We may collect certain information from you when you access and use the Platform, including when you are using the Platform without an account. Such information includes your IP address, mobile carrier, time zone settings, the version of the app you are using, model of your device, the device system, network type, device IDs, your screen resolution, and operating system. Where you log-in from multiple devices, we will be able to use your profile information to identify your activity across devices. Moreover, we automatically collect information related to performance, device or system errors, and other technical information for diagnostic measurement and troubleshooting.
* Location. We collect information about your approximate location, including location information based on your SIM card and/or IP address. Where location services are available for the Lemon8 app in your region, and if you choose to turn it on, we will receive your precise or approximate location information from your device's GPS data. In addition, we collect location information (such as tourist attractions, or other points of interest) if you choose to add location information to your User Content.
* Image and Audio Information. Where permitted in your region, we may collect information about the videos, images and audio that are a part of your User Content, such as identifying the objects and scenery that appear, the existence and location within an image of face and body features and attributes, the nature of the audio, and the text of the words spoken in your User Content. We may collect this information to enable image and video effects, to improve safety and user experience, to moderate content consistent with our [Community Guidelines](https://www.lemon8-app.com/community-guideline?region=us&language=en) and, to recommend content, for analytics, and to support special features, such as providing beauty tips based on the shape of your face and your complexion (available only in some regions). We do not use any face information to identify you or other people in your videos or photos, nor do we share such information with third parties. Any face or voice information collected to support special features will be deleted promptly after we provide you with such features, except where you request that we save your information.
* Inferred Information: We may make inferences about you, such as your interests, based on information we collect.
* Cookies. We and our vendors and service providers use cookies and other similar technologies (e.g., web beacons, flash cookies, etc.) (“Cookies”) to automatically collect information, measure and analyze which web pages you click on and how you use the Platform, enhance your experience using the Platform, and improve our services. Cookies are small files which, when placed on your device, enable the Platform to provide certain features and functionality. Web beacons are very small images or small pieces of data embedded in images, also known as “pixel tags” or “clear GIFs,” that can recognize Cookies, the time and date a page is viewed, a description of the page where the pixel tag is placed, and similar information from your computer or device. We will obtain your consent to our use of Cookies where required by law. Unless stated otherwise in a relevant part of the Supplemental Terms - Jurisdiction Specific, by using the Platform, you consent to our use of Cookies. To learn how to disable certain Cookies, see the [<Your Choices>](#your-choices) section below. Additionally, we allow our business partners and other vendors and service providers (including analytics vendors and service providers) to collect information about your online activities through Cookies. We are not responsible for the privacy practices of these third parties, and the information practices of these third parties are not covered by this Privacy Policy.

**2\. How we use your personal information**
--------------------------------------------

We use your information to improve, support and administer the Platform, to allow you to use its functionalities, to fulfill and enforce our [Terms of Service](https://www.lemon8-app.com/legal/terms-of-service?region=us&language=en), and for the following purposes:

* fulfill requests for products, services, Platform functionality, support internal operations, including troubleshooting, data analysis, testing, research, statistical, and survey purposes and to solicit your feedback;
* customize and personalize the content you see on the Platform;
* support the social functions of the Platform, including to enable you to share User Content and interact with other users;
* enable you to send and receive messages if you use this function;
* to train and improve our technology, such as our machine learning models and algorithms.
* communicate with you, including to notify you about changes to our service;
* detect abuse, fraud and illegal activity on the Platform;
* promote the safety and security of the Platform, including by scanning, analyzing, and reviewing User Content, messages and associated metadata for potential breach of our [Terms of Service](https://www.lemon8-app.com/legal/terms-of-service?region=us&language=en), [Community Guidelines](https://www.lemon8-app.com/community-guideline?region=us&language=en), other conditions and policies, and other inappropriate content;
* ensure content is presented in the most effective manner for you and your device;
* improve, promote, and develop the Platform and promote popular topics, hashtags and campaigns on the Platform including through the use of contests and promotions;
* understand how you use the Platform, including across your devices;
* carry out data analysis, research and investigations, and test the Platform to ensure its stability and security;
* allow you to participate in interactive features of the Platform;
* verify your identity where applicable and ensure that you are old enough to use our Platform (as required by law);
* provide you with location-based services (where those services are available in your jurisdiction);
* comply with our legal obligations, or as necessary to perform tasks in the public interest, or to protect the vital interests of our users and other people;
* infer additional information about you, such as your interests in order to personalize the content you see on the Platform;
* combine the information we collect or receive about you for the purposes listed above;

We may also use your personal information for other purposes disclosed to you at the time we collect your information or pursuant to your consent where required by law.

**3\. How we share your personal information**
----------------------------------------------

Business Partners

Where available, if you choose to register to use the Platform using your social network account details (e.g., Facebook, Apple, TikTok, Google, or Twitter) or link your Lemon8 account with other social network accounts, you will provide us or allow your social network to provide us with your username and public profile. We will likewise share certain information with the relevant social network such as your app ID, access token and the referring URL.

Where you opt to share content to third party social media platforms, the content, username and accompanying text will be shared on that platform or, if you opt to share content via a third party instant messaging platform such as WhatsApp, a link to your Platform content will be shared but not the content itself.

Service Providers

We provide information and content to service providers who support our business, such as analytics providers to help us in the optimisation and improvement of the Platform.

Our Corporate Group

As a global company, the Platform may be supported by certain entities within our corporate group. These entities will process your information to enable them to provide certain important functions, such as by improving and optimizing the Platform and supporting users.

Legal Obligations and Rights

We may share your information with law enforcement agencies, public authorities or other parties if legally required to do so, or if we have a good faith belief that such sharing is necessary to:

* comply with any applicable laws, regulations, codes of practice, governmental guidelines, or other legal and regulatory obligations, as consistent with internationally recognised standards;
* enforce our [Terms of Service](https://www.lemon8-app.com/legal/terms-of-service?region=us&language=en) and other agreements, policies, and standards, including investigation of any potential violation thereof;
* exercise or defend any legal claims, including to respond to subpoenas, court orders, legal process, law enforcement requests, legal claims, or government inquiries;
* detect, prevent or otherwise address security, fraud, copyright infringement or other illegal activity or technical issues; or
* protect the rights, property or safety of us, our users, copyright holders, a third party or the public as required or permitted by law (including exchanging information with other companies and organizations for the purposes of fraud protection and credit risk reduction).

Corporate Transactions

* We may share the categories of personal information listed above in connection with a substantial corporate transaction, such as the sale of a website, a merger, consolidation, asset sales, or in the unlikely event of bankruptcy.

With Your Consent

We may share your information for other purposes with your consent or at your direction. Where we obtain your consent you will always be able to revoke your consent.

Public Activities

If you choose to engage in public activities on the Platform, you should be aware that any information you share may be read, collected, or used by other users, as well as third parties such as search engines, content aggregators and news sites. You should use caution in disclosing personal information while using the Platform. We are not responsible for the information you choose to publish. You can control whether to make your profile information and User Content public or private in the settings menu.

**4\. Your Rights**
-------------------

You have rights and choices when it comes to your information. You may be afforded certain rights under applicable laws, which may include the right to access, delete, update, or rectify your data, to be informed of the processing of your data, to file complaints with authorities, and potentially other rights. Please note that your exercise of certain rights may impact your ability to use some or all of our features and functionalities.

For more details about your rights, please refer to the "Supplemental Terms - Jurisdiction Specific" section below.

Please contact us by using the contact information provided in the “Contact Us” section if you would like to exercise any of your rights. We will respond to your request consistent with applicable law and subject to proper verification.

**5\. Your Choices**
--------------------

* You may be able to refuse or disable Cookies by adjusting your browser settings. Because each browser is different, please consult the instructions provided by your browser. Please note that your opt-out selection is specific to the particular browser or device that you are using when you opt out, so you may need to opt-out separately for each browser or device. If you choose to refuse, disable, or delete Cookies, some of the functionality of the Platform may no longer be available to you. If you are located in the UK, please visit the “UK” [<Supplemental Terms - Jurisdiction Specific>](https://www.lemon8-app.com/legal/privacy?region=us&language=en) of this policy for more information about how you can manage your Cookie preferences. You can control and access some of your personal information by signing into the Platform. For example, you can delete the User Content you uploaded. We also provide a number of tools in the Settings section of the Platform that allow you to control your privacy preferences, such as who can view your User Content. Should you choose to do so, you may delete your entire account in Settings. If you have any questions on how to use those tools, or want to exercise any rights you may have in the country where you live, please contact us at [contact@lemon8-app.com](mailto:contact@lemon8-app.com).

**6\. Data Security and Retention**
-----------------------------------

We take steps to ensure that your information is treated securely and in accordance with this policy. Unfortunately, the transmission of information via the internet is not completely secure. We cannot guarantee the security of your information transmitted via the Platform.

We maintain appropriate technical, administrative, and physical security measures that are designed to protect your information from unauthorized access, theft, disclosure, modification, or loss. We maintain these technical and organizational measures and will amend them from time to time to improve the overall security of our systems.

We will, from time to time, include links to and from the websites of third parties. If you follow a link to any of these websites, please note that these websites have their own privacy policies and that we do not accept any responsibility or liability for these policies. Please check these policies before you submit any information to these websites.

We retain your information for as long as it is necessary to provide you with the service and for the other purposes set out in this Privacy Policy or as may be required by law.

The retention periods will be different depending on the type of information and the purposes for which we use the information. For example, when we process your information to provide you with the Platform, we keep information such as your account and profile information for as long as you have an account.

**7\. International Data Transfers**
------------------------------------

The personal information we collect from you may be stored on a server located outside of the country where you live. We store the information we collect in secure servers located in the United States and Singapore. Where we transfer any personal information out of the country where you live, including for one or more of the purposes as set out in this Policy, we will do so in accordance with the requirements of applicable data protection laws.

**8\. Information Relating to Minors**
--------------------------------------

Lemon8 is not directed at children under the age of 13. The minimum age to use the Platform may differ depending on the country or region you are in. If you believe that we have collected personal information from a minor under the minimum age, please contact us at [contact@lemon8-app.com](mailto:contact@lemon8-app.com).

**9\. Privacy Policy Updates**
------------------------------

We may amend or update this Privacy Policy from time to time. When we update the Privacy Policy, we will notify you of any material changes to this policy by updating the “Last Updated” date at the top of the new Privacy Policy, posting the new Privacy Policy, or providing any other notice required by applicable law. We recommend that you review this policy regularly to stay informed of our privacy practices.

**10\. Contact Us**
-------------------

Questions, comments and requests regarding this policy should be addressed to [contact@lemon8-app.com](mailto:contact@lemon8-app.com).

**SUPPLEMENTAL TERMS – JURISDICTION SPECIFIC**

In the event of a conflict between the provisions of the Supplemental Terms – Jurisdiction Specific that are relevant to your jurisdiction from which you access or use the Platform, and the rest of the Policy, the relevant jurisdiction’s Supplemental Terms – Jurisdiction Specific will supersede and control.

Indonesia

If you are using our services in Indonesia, the following additional terms apply. In the event of any conflict between the following additional terms and the provisions of the main body of this policy, the following terms shall apply.

Age, Parental and Guardian Consent. By accessing and/or using this Platform, you represent that you are at least 21 years of age or married or not under guardianship. If you are below 21 years old and you are not married, or under guardianship:

* you must obtain approval from your parent(s) or legal guardian(s); and
* your parent(s) or legal guardian(s) are responsible for: (i) all your actions in connection with your access to and use of the Platform; (ii) your compliance with this policy; and (iii) ensuring that any of your participation in the Platform will not, in any event, result in any violation of applicable laws and regulations relating to child protections.

If you do not have consent from your parent(s) or legal guardian(s) and your parent(s) or guardian(s) is not willing to open the account under their name, you must cease accessing the Platform.

Your Choices. You may withdraw your consent to Lemon8’s disclosure of personal data to third parties. Upon your request, we will cease to display, publish, transmit, disseminate, and/or open the access to your personal data to third parties. Please note that by withdrawing your consent to the disclosure and/or collection of your personal data, we may not be able to fulfill your requests and you may not be able to use some of Lemon8 features and functionality. You may request Lemon8 to (i) disclose the history of personal data that we have collected; and/or (ii) erase and dispose of your personal data that we have collected on our server. Please note that by requesting us to erase and dispose of your personal data, you may not be able to use some of Lemon8’s features and functionality. Please use the contact information for your region provided in the “Contact Us” section if you would like to exercise any of your rights.

Notification. In the event of any breach of personal data, we will notify you and provide you with information regarding such breach of personal data.

Data Retention. We retain your information for as long as it is necessary to provide you with the service. Where we do not need your information in order to provide the service to you, we retain it only for so long as we have a legitimate business purpose in keeping such data. However, there are occasions where we are likely to keep this data for five (5) years (or longer if required) in accordance with our legal obligations or where it is necessary for the establishment, exercise or defence of legal claims. After you have terminated your use of our Platform and the five (5) years retention period has lapsed, we store your information in an aggregated and anonymised format. Non-personally identifiable information may be retained indefinitely for analytics.

Philippines

If you are using the Platform in Philippines, the following additional terms shall apply pursuant to the relevant laws, rules and regulations and issuances by the Philippines National Privacy Commission (“NPC”) on data privacy. Your Rights. To the extent that the relevant laws, rules and regulations on data privacy recognize your rights and freedoms as data subjects, you shall have the right to information, object, access, rectification, erasure or blocking, lodge complaints before the NPC, damages and data portability. Before we can respond to a request to exercise one or more of the rights listed above, you may be required to verify your identity or your account details.

UK

The minimum age to use the Platform in the UK is 18. If you are using the Platform in the UK the following additional terms apply:

Legal bases for processing

We use your personal data only as permitted by law. Our legal bases for processing your information are described in the table below.

| **Processing purpose** | **Legal basis** |
| --- | --- |
| We use your information, for example:* when registering an account;<br>* when logging in, signing up, or linking to the Platform via third party accounts;<br>* when using the Platform;<br>* when completing transactions;<br>* your location;<br>* when sending messages on the Platform;<br>* when contacting us;<br>* from other sources; and<br>* from your device or app<br>to enable us to deliver the Platform , including to create accounts, process your transactions, facilitate social connections on the Platform, and to deliver a fast and convenient logging-in experience. | Processing is necessary to perform the contract governing our provision of the Platform or to take steps that you request prior to signing up for an account to use the Platform. |
| We use your information, for example:* when logging in, signing up, or linking to the Platform via third party accounts;<br>* when using the Platform;<br>* when completing transactions;<br>* when sending messages on the Platform;<br>* when contacting us;from other sources; and<br>* from your device or app<br>to understand how you use the Platform, including reviewing user feedback. | The processing is necessary for our legitimate interests, namely, to identify and resolve issues with the Platform. |
| We use your information, for example:* when registering an account;<br>* when logging in, signing up, or linking to the Platform via third party accounts;<br>* when using the Platform;<br>* when completing transactions;<br>* your location;<br>* when sending messages on the Platform;<br>* when contacting us;from other sources; and<br>* from your device or app<br>to enable us to review, improve, promote and develop our Platform to better serve you and the Lemon8 community, including by performing analytics. | The processing is necessary for our legitimate interests, namely, to improve the Platform. |
| The categories of information that we use will depend on the specific circumstances of each request or obligation. Depending on the circumstances, we could use the your information, for example:* when registering an account;when logging in, signing up, or linking to the Platform via third party accounts;<br>* when using the Platform;when completing transactions;<br>* your location;<br>* when sending messages on the Platform;<br>* when contacting us;<br>* from other sources; and<br>* from your device or app<br>to comply with our legal obligations and rights, including where necessary to assist in law enforcement and investigations conducted by any governmental and/or regulatory authority. | In some circumstances, this processing is necessary in order to comply with our legal obligations. This includes situations where we have obligations to take measures to ensure the safety of our users or comply with a valid legal request such as an order from law enforcement agencies or courts.In other circumstances, the processing is necessary for our legitimate interests, namely, to disclose and share information with regulators or other government entities. |
| We use your information, for example:* when registering an account;<br>* when contacting us; and<br>* from your device or app<br>* to communicate with you, including to notify you about changes to the Platform, provide customer support to you and send you other service-related messages. | The processing is necessary for the performance of a contract with you. |
| We use your information, for example:* when registering an account;<br>* when logging in, signing up, or linking to the Platform via third party accounts;<br>* when using the Platform;<br>* when completing transactions;<br>* your location;<br>* when sending messages on the Platform;<br>* when contacting us;<br>* from other sources; and<br>* from your device or app<br>to send you marketing communications in accordance with your preferences. | The processing is necessary for our legitimate interests, namely to promote new developments and features of the Platform. We will obtain your consent to send you messages where required by law. |
| We use your information, for example:* when registering an account;<br>* when logging in, signing up, or linking to the Platform via third party accounts;<br>* when using the Platform;<br>* when completing transactions;<br>* your location;<br>* when sending messages on the Platform;<br>* when contacting us;<br>* from other sources; and<br>* from your device or app<br>to enforce our terms, conditions and policies, including to ensure that you are old enough to use the Platform. | The processing is necessary for the performance of a contract with you. |
| We use your information, for example:* when registering an account;<br>* when logging in, signing up, or linking to the Platform via third party accounts;<br>* when using the Platform;<br>* when completing transactions;<br>* your location;<br>* When sending messages on the Platform;<br>* when contacting us;<br>* from other sources; and<br>* from your device or app<br>to promote the safety, security, and stability of the Platform, such as by preventing and detecting fraud. | The processing is necessary for our legitimate interests, namely, to ensure that the Platform is safe and secure. In some circumstances this processing may also be necessary for the performance of a contract with you. |
| In some cases, we may aggregate or anonymise your information and use it in a way that is designed to be unable to identify you, for research or other purposes, to the extent allowed by applicable law. | The processing is necessary for our legitimate interests, namely to conduct research and protect personal information through aggregation or anonymization, consistent with data minimization and privacy by design principles. |
| We may use your information where it is necessary to protect your or someone else's life, physical integrity, or safety. This could include providing law enforcement agencies or emergency services with information in urgent situations to protect health or life. The specific types of information we use will depend on the specific situation. | The processing is necessary to protect the vital interests of you or other individuals. |

International data transfers

As a global business, the personal information that we collect about you may be further transferred to, and stored at, a destination outside of the UK to provide our Platform.

We may store the information that we collect in secure servers located in the United States and Singapore.

Certain entities in our Corporate Group may also receive or have access to this information so they can provide certain functions, as described in the our Corporate Group section.

We share information with service providers, business partners and other third parties, as described in [<How we share your personal information>](#how-we-share-your-personal-information). These third parties may be located outside the UK.

When we transfer your information outside of the UK, we ensure it benefits from an adequate level of data protection by relying on:

* Adequacy decisions. These are “adequacy regulations” from the UK Secretary of State under Article 45 UK GDPR where they recognise that a country offers an adequate level of data protection. We transfer your information as described in What Information We Collect to some countries with adequacy decisions; or
* Standard contractual clauses and UK Addendum. Under Article 46 of the UK GDPR the Information Commissioner has recognised the EU approved contractual clauses as providing protection for data transferred outside the UK, subject to the completion of the UK Addendum we rely on standard contractual clauses and the UK Addendum to transfer information as described in What Information We Collect to certain entities in our Corporate Group and third parties in countries without an adequacy decision.

For a copy of these adequacy decisions or standard contractual clauses/UK addendum, please contact us by using the contact information for your region provided in the “Contact Us” section.

Your rights

You have the following rights:

* The right to request proper rectification or erasure of your personal information or restriction of the processing of your personal information;
* Where processing of your personal information is either based on your consent or necessary for the performance of a contract with you and processing is carried out by automated means, the right to receive the personal information concerning you in a structured, commonly used and machine-readable format or to have your personal data transmitted directly to another company, where technically feasible (data portability);
* Where the processing of your personal information is based on your consent, the right to withdraw your consent at any time (withdrawal will not impact the lawfulness of data processing activities that have taken place before such withdrawal);
* The right to object to processing if we are processing your personal information on the basis of our legitimate interest unless we can demonstrate compelling legitimate grounds which may override your right. If you object to such processing, we ask you to state the grounds of your objection in order for us to examine the processing of your personal information and to balance our legitimate interest in processing and your objection to this processing;
* You have the right to request the restriction of the processing of your information where (a) you are challenging the accuracy of the information, (b) the information has been unlawfully processed, but you are opposing the deletion of that information, (c) where you need the information to be retained for the pursuit or defence of a legal claim, or (d) you have objected to processing and you are awaiting the outcome of that objection request.
* The right to object to processing your personal information for direct marketing purposes; and
* The right to lodge complaints before your local supervisory authority in the UK or in your Member State through your local representative.

Before we can respond to a request to exercise one or more of the rights listed above, you may be required to verify your identity or your account details.

Please use the contact information provided in the “Contact Us” section if you would like to exercise any of your rights.

If you are based in the United Kingdom, our designated UK GDPR representative is:

Cosmo Technology Private Limited 2 Temple Back East Temple Quay Bristol United Kingdom BS1 6EG

We will, unless exempt, obtain your consent to the use of Cookies. For more information about cookies, please visit our Cookies Policy: [https://www.lemon8-app.com/legal/cookies-policy](https://www.lemon8-app.com/legal/cookies-policy?region=us&language=en)

United States

The minimum age to use the Platform in the United States is 18. If you are using the Platform in the United States, the following additional terms apply:

Your Rights and Choices Depending on where you live, you may be entitled to certain rights with respect to your personal information, as described below:

* Right to Know. You may have the right to know what personal information we have collected about you, including the categories of personal information, the categories of sources from which it is collected, the business or commercial purposes for collecting, selling, or sharing it, and the categories of third parties to whom we disclose it.
* Access and Data Portability. Subject to certain exceptions, you may have the right to request a copy of the personal information that we collected about you during the 12 months before your request.
* Deletion. You may have the right to request that we delete information that we collected from or about you, subject to certain exceptions.
* Correct Inaccurate Information. You may have the right to request that we correct inaccuracies in the personal information we maintain about you.

For United States users, the Platform does not sell your personal information or share your personal information with third parties for purposes of cross-context behavioral advertising or targeted advertising where restricted by applicable law.  
Although some of the information we collect may be considered sensitive personal information, we only process such information in order to provide the Platform and within other exemptions under applicable law, such as when we process your sensitive personal information in order to perform the services or provide the goods you request from us.  
You may exercise these rights by contacting us at the information listed in the “Contact Us” section.  
You may be entitled, in accordance with applicable law, to submit a request through an authorized agent. To designate an authorized agent to exercise choices on your behalf, please provide evidence that you have given such agent power of attorney or that the agent otherwise has valid written authority to submit requests to exercise rights on your behalf.  
We will respond to your request consistent with applicable law and subject to proper verification. We will verify your request by asking you to send it from the email address associated with your account or to provide information necessary to verify your account.  
You may appeal any decision we have made about your request by replying to the communication you receive from us communicating your decision. We will not discriminate against you for exercising your rights and choices, although some of the functionality and features available on this Platform may change or no longer be available to you.  
Other California Rights

* Your browser may offer you a “Do Not Track” option, which allows you to signal to operators of websites and web applications and services that you do not wish such operators to track certain of your online activities over time and/or across different websites. Our products do not support Do Not Track requests at this time.
* You may have the right to request that we disclose the categories of personal information we have shared with third parties for the third parties’ direct marketing purposes. You may exercise this right by contacting us at the information listed in the “Contact Us” section.

Vietnam

If you are using the Platform in Vietnam, the following additional terms apply:

Age, Parental and Guardian Consent. By accessing and/or using the Platform, you represent that you are at least 16 years of age or not under guardianship. If you are below 16 years old or under guardianship:

* you must obtain approval from your parent(s) or legal guardian(s); and
* your parent(s) or legal guardian(s) are responsible for: (i) all your actions in connection with your access to and use of the Platform; (ii) your compliance with this policy; and (iii) ensuring that any of your participation in the Platform will not, in any event, result in any violation of applicable laws and regulations relating to child protections.

If you do not have consent from your parent(s) or legal guardian(s) and your parent(s) or legal guardian(s) is not willing to open the account under their name, you must cease accessing the Platform.
